Raoul family papers, 1865-1985
Emory University
- Miscellaneous, 1881-1982, Series 4; Box 46; OP 7-10
  - Fiction, 1973-2006, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 15-45; OP1-5
    - Grimus (1975)
Baldwin, Roger Nash, 1884- Series 1 - 17:16 (19)
Beaman, Charles Colesworth, 1840-1900 Series 1 - 2:3 (2)
Brown, Joseph Emerson, 1821-1894 Series 1 - 2:1 (1); 2:3 (1)
Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925 Series 1: 2:5 (2) Series 2: 38:8 (2)
Calhoun, Abner Wellborn, 1846-1910 Series 1 - 7:8 (2)
Catt, Carrie Lane Chapman, 1859-1947 Series 1 - 31:3 (2); 33:1 (3)
Cavalier Corporation, Chattanooga, Tennessee SEE Series 1.6
Corput, Felix Van Den, 1840- Series 1 - 2:1 (1)
Culver Military Academy, Culver, Indiana SEE Series 1.13
Diaz, Porfirio, Pres. Mexico, 1830-1915 Series 1 - 2:4 (1); 2:5 (1)
Downing, W. T. SEE Series 3
Druid Hills SEE Series 4
Eleazer, Robert Burns, 1877- Series 1 - 17:16 (1)
Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, Georgia SEE Series 1.7
Gilbert, Bradford, 1853-1911 SEE Series 1.5; 1.7; 4
Glenn, Thomas Kearney, 1868-1946 SEE Series 1.9
Goethals, George Washington, 1858-1928 Series 1 - 16:11 (1)
Hanson, John Fletcher, 1840- Series 1 - 2:1 (1); 2:3 (2)
Hartsfield, William Berry, 1890-1971 Series 1 - 32:11 (1)
Haygood, Atticus Greene, 1839-1896 Series 1 - 2:2 (1)
Hepburn, Katharine, 1909- Series 1 - 31:5 (1)
Irwin County Cotton Mills, Waycross, Georgia SEE Series 1.5
J. F. Minis Company, Savannah, Georgia SEE Series 1.6
Kennedy, Stetson Series 1 - 31:8 (1)
Keyser Manufacturing Company, Chattanooga, Tennessee SEE Series 1.6
Longstreet, Helen Dortch (Mrs. James) Series 1 - 34:10 (1)
Loomis Sanatorium, New York, New York SEE Series 1.10
McIntosh, Henry Martyn, 1852- Series 1 - 2:1 (1)
Millis, Walter, 1899- Series 1 - 31:2 (1); 31:6 (15); 31:7 (7) Series 2 - 36:10 (7)
Odorless Refrigerator Company, Chattanooga, Tennessee SEE Series 1.6; 1.13
Park, Robert Emory, d. 1909 Series 1 - 2:1 (1)
Patterson, Hannah Jane, 1879-1937 Series 1 - 30:5 (1); 33:1 (2)
Paul, Alice Series 1 - 31:1 (2)
Peabody, George Foster, 1852-1938 Series 1 - 31:1 (1) Peacock School, Atlanta, Georgia SEE Series 1.11
Pratt Institute, New York, New York SEE Series 1.10
Ramspeck, Robert, 1890- Series 1 - 30:19 (1)
Russell, Richard Brevard, 1897-1971 Series 1 - 30:19 (1)
S. M. Inman and Company, Macon, Georgia SEE Series 1.7
St. Joseph's Sanatorium, Asheville, North Carolina SEE Series 1.10
Saint Timothy's School, Baltimore, Maryland SEE Series 1.12
Senior, Clarence Ollson, 1903 Series 1 - 17:17 (11); 17:18 (8); 17:19 (15)
Sherwin, Belle, 1868-1955 Series 1 - 34:1 (1)
Shuler, Nettie Rogers, 1862-1939 Series 1 - 33:1 (1)
South Atlantic Car and Manufacturing Company, Waycross, Georgia SEE Series 1.5
Southern Saw Works, East Point, Georgia SEE Series 1.5
Tennessee Furniture Corporation, Chattanooga, Tennessee SEE Series 1.6
Trammell, Leander Newton, 1830-1900 Series 1 - 2:1 (1)
Veltin School, New York, New York SEE Series 1.10; 1.12
Wadley, William Morrill Series 1 - 2:1 (1) Series 2 - 39:11 (10)
Washington Seminary, Atlanta, Georgia SEE Series 1.8; 1.9; 1.12
Watson, Thomas Edward, 1856-1922 Series 1 - 2:5 (1)
Wilkins, Josephine Mathewson, 1896-1977 Series 1 - 31:3 (1)
Willingham, Calder Baynard, 1852-1908 Series 1 - 2:1 (1)
Woodberry Forest School, Orange, Virginia SEE Series 1.11; 1.13
Woolford, T. Guy Series 1 - 32:4 (10); 32:5 (3)
Second Index
Guy, Some Other